We just survived a bombing in Arrimal here in Gaza City.
This is the second bombing that happened in less than 30 minutes.
I was standing next to the door of a gift shop preparing for Eid Al-Adha,
just like everyone else here in Gaza.
Then I hear a boom and I saw a light and then there was shrapnel and I was pushed back
into the gift shop and then we see water on the sidewalk and this is what happened.
We just survived the massacre. We were literally in the same building that they just bombed.
They bombed the top of the building up here and there are people that are going to check if there
are any survivors. Thankfully we survived and we're okay but our adrenaline is going and
we just survived another massacre. This is the reality that we constantly are living under.
This is the second bombing that happened in less than 30 minutes.
The ambulance is just arriving just in case people need medical attention.